瑞典
Uh, Sweden.
我们说瑞典语
I'm... I'm... Swedish
但我会说一点英语
but I speak a little English.
我们要上船
We're coming on board.
欢迎大家 欢迎大家
All are welcome. All are welcome.
可爱的小家伙 都上来吧
Even the little one. He can come too.
欢迎
Welcome.
你为什么来这里
Why are you here?
一个小小的航海假期
Just a little sailing holiday.
专属男孩之旅
A jolly boys trip.
手拿开
Take your hands off.
有无文件
Papers?
护照
Passport?
拿去
Here you go.
船上还有其他人吗
Any other people on the boat?
只有我们两个人
Just the two of us.
不
Nein.
快来 我们有很多好吃的
Come, come, we have lots to eat...
把你的脏手拿开
Take your dirty hands off me!
退后
Back off!
还有你
And you,
把手举起来
put your hands in the air!
哦
Ooh!
你现在有麻烦了
You're in trouble now!
真是个淘气的孩子
You've been a naughty boy!
我给你100法郎 杀了他
I'll give you 100 francs to shoot him.
别开枪
Don't shoot me!
他讨厌德国人 真该一枪毙了他
He hates Germans. You should really shoot him.
对不起 你太吓人了
I... I'm sorry. You are very scary.
让他走板子
Make him walk the plank.
他会喜欢的
He loves wood.
肮脏的酒鬼
Dirty drunken animal!
罪名成立
Guilty as charged.
我总是带一罐煤油
I always take a can of kerosene
就是为这种场合准备的
for just these sort of occasions.
有一段时间了
It's been a while,
上次有人嘲笑我时
but the last time someone laughed at me
当我登上他们的船时
when I boarded their vessel,
我给了他们选择
I gave them the choice.
要么游上岸
Either swim to shore
要么在船上烧死
or take their chances on a burning ship.
汉斯和我都想知道 他们会选择哪种
Hans and I wondered which option they'd choose,
死于水或死于火
death by water or death by fire.
但很奇怪 他们都选了
Oddly, they chose both.
他们一直等到最后一刻
They waited until the very last moment,
直到头发着火
until their hair was on fire,
他们的手指被水泡得皮开肉绽
and their blistered skin peeled from their fingers,
在他们浸入水中之前
before they immersed themselves in water
一切都是妄想
in the vain hope
无法到达岸边
of reaching shore.
其中之一
One of them
沉没并葬身鱼腹
sank immediately and perished.
但令我们惊奇的是 他很顽强
But to our amazement, the big one,
表现出了伟大的精神
he showed great spirit.
尽管困难重重
In spite of all the odds...
他费尽周折上了岸
...he painstakingly made it to shore.
我们紧随其后 为他欢呼
We followed and cheered him on
并奖励了他 令人印象深刻的一幕
and rewarded this impressive achievement
用子弹
with a bullet
打穿他的后脑
to the back of his head.
不是很有趣吗
Isn't that funny?
你为什么不笑
Why aren't you laughing?
干得好 拉森
Nice work, Lassen.
还有更多
There's more where that came from.
是的
Yes.
啊
Ah...
不知道有无效果 拉森
Not sure it's working, Lassen.
船长看起来相当激动
The captain looks rather agitated.
他们把枪都拿出来了
They're bringing their guns to bear.
他们很快就会射到我们 长官
They'll find their range soon, sir.
弗雷迪 我们应该担心吗
Freddy, should we be worried?
哦 我不这么认为 长官
Oh, I don't think so, sir.
相当大的爆炸物 设置了相当大的引信
It's a rather large explosive, so I set a rather large fuse.
我定位到了房间的外面
I located the outside of the powder room,
所以当它爆炸时
so when it goes bang,
效果应该很棒
it really should go bang.
快一点
Closer...
马上就好了 伙计们
Should be any second now, chaps.
弗雷迪
Freddy?
干得好 弗雷德里克
Good work, Frederick.
谢谢你 船长
Thank you, Captain.
现在 能不能告诉我们
Now, any chance you can tell us
我们在这里做什么 长官
what we're doing here, sir?
欧战仍在继续
The war in Europe rages on
希特勒和他的纳粹大军横扫千军
as Hitler and his Nazi horde sweep aside all in their path.
波兰 比利时和现在的法国
Poland, Belgium and now France
都倒向了希特勒的法西斯政权
have all fallen to Hitler's fascist regime,
留给英国最后的希望
leaving Britain holding up the final hopes
能否解放全欧洲
of liberation for all of Europe.
英国 准备好战斗吧
So, come on, Blighty, get ready for a fighty.
但我们无法独自做到这一点
But we cannot do it alone.
来自美国兄弟的帮助
And any hope for our American brothers
从大西洋彼岸加入我们的行列
to join us from across the Atlantic
坏消息
remains frustrated
德国的秘密武器U型潜艇
by Germany's secret weapon, the U-boat.
俗称致命小潜艇
These deadly little submarines
在北大西洋任意搅局
hunt at will in the North Atlantic.
U型潜艇无法被发现 它肆意击沉船只
Undetectable, the U-boat sinks ships indiscriminately,
无论是运载弹药 辎重
whether carrying munitions, provisions
或平民的转移
or civilians heading
来自我们对岸的同伴
from our companions across the pond.
只要U型潜艇还统治着大西洋
So long as the U-boats rule the Atlantic,
一切都不可能
it remains impossible
让美国勇敢的军队到达我们的海岸
for America's brave troops to reach our shores.
英国是否会接受希特勒的计划
Will Britain be forced to appease Hitler's plans
还是面临其攻势的毁灭性打击
or face devastation from his offensive?
伦敦在燃烧 大海在变红
London burns and her seas run red,
上有炸弹 下有鱼雷
as bombs from above and torpedoes from below
正在肆虐英国人
grind the Brits down.
面对这些致命的武器 毫无招架之力
And with no defense against these lethal U-boats,
看来希望渺茫
it appears all hope may be lost
欧洲永无和平
for peace in Europe.
德国人用U型潜艇切断了我们的供应链
The Germans cut off our supply chain with U-boats,
我们切断了U型潜艇的供应链
we cut off the supply chain to the U-boats.
通过情报人员
Through our intelligence agents,
我们找到办法了
we've found a way.
整个
The entire
保养 维修和重装
servicing, repairing, and rearming
希特勒的大西洋U型潜艇舰队
of Hitler's Atlantic U-boat fleet...
由两艘纳粹拖船操作
is operated by two Nazi tug boats...
和一艘意大利补给船
and an Italian supply ship in Fernando Po.
我需要人手击沉那些船只
I need men who are willing to go and sink those ships.
我们为什么不直接空袭费尔南多波
Why don't we just air-raid Fernando Po
并击沉船只
and sink the ships?
因为德国人很狡猾
Because crafty Germans, being crafty Germans,
将自己掩护于西班牙的殖民地
have positioned themselves in a Spanish colony.
费尔南多波是中立地带
Fernando Po is neutral territory.
如果我们攻击殖民地
If we attack that colony,
其余未被占领的欧洲将加入纳粹
the rest of unoccupied Europe will join the Nazis,
只是时间问题
and it's only a question of time
在我们找到方法之前
before we find ourselves
只能煎粉红色大香肠
frying big pink sausages
穿着莱德松
wearing nothing but lederhosen.
希特勒不按规矩办事
Hitler is not playing by the rules
我们也一样
and neither are we.
这当然是未经批准的
This will of course be an unsanctioned,
未经授权的非正式任务
unauthorized and unofficial mission.
如果他们被英国人俘虏了
If they're captured by the British,
会被关进监狱
they'll be thrown in jail.
但如果纳粹找到他们
But if the Nazis find them...
便是折磨和死亡
it's torture and death.
难搞
Somewhat contentiously,
我可能就是那个人
I may have just the man,
一切颇为不妥
but rather inconveniently,
他目前正被监禁 听候发落
he's currently incarcerated at His Majesty's pleasure.
我们可能不喜欢他的态度
We may not like his attitude,
但他很大胆 是个杀手
but he's bold, he's a killer,
人们会跟随他到任何地方
and the men will follow him anywhere.
我们确定这是个好主意吗
Are we sure this is a good idea?
当然不是
Of course we're not.
但我们已经走投无路
But we're desperate.
让他进来
Send him in.
往前走
Forward!
站在那里 少校
Stand there, Major.
谢谢你 警长
Thank you, Sergeant.
古斯-马奇-菲利普斯
Gus March-Phillips,
这是中校
this is Lieutenant Commander...
弗莱明伊恩-弗莱明
Fleming. Ian Fleming.
他以前在海军情报局工作
He used to be at Naval Intelligence,
现在他为我工作
now he works for me.
我为什么在这里
Why am I here, M?
我有一项任务需要你去完成
I have a mission I want you to lead.
为什么是我
Why are you asking me, M?
请自便 少校
Help yourself to a cup of tea, Major.
他们都知道
We both know that I'm...
行政部门不太喜欢我
not very popular with the administration.
因为他们觉得你没有吸引力
The reason they find you unattractive
而我喜欢你的魅力
is the very reason I find you attractive.
这项任务
Mission?
邮差行动
Operation Postmaster.
消灭德国U型潜艇的威胁
To neutralize the German U-boats
在北大西洋
in the North Atlantic.
计划是什么
And, uh, what's the plan?
U型潜艇需要
The U-boats need
燃料和鱼雷 哦
- fuel and torpedoes. - Oh.
但他们也需要
But they also need
氧气 二氧化碳过滤器
carbon dioxide filters for oxygen.
没有它们就无法潜水 也无法攻击
Without them, they can't dive and they can't hunt.
当浮在水面时 它们就没有威胁了
Stuck on the surface, they're obsolete.
目标呢
Target?
奥斯塔公爵夫人
The Duchessa d'Aosta.
是一艘意大利船 德国人一直在使用
She's an Italian ship the Germans have been using...
加油 重新武装和补给
...to refuel, re-arm and replenish
整个车队的二氧化碳过滤器
the CO2 filters for the entire fleet.
她藏在西非海岸附近
She's hidden off the coast of West Africa.
一个名叫费尔南多波的小岛
A small island called Fernando Po.
把她击沉
We want you to, um, sink her.
你们将冒充渔民
You'll be posing as fishermen
在西海岸航行
sailing down the west coast
在一艘拖网渔船上装载了足够的炸药
on board a trawler loaded with enough explosives
摧毁公爵夫人号
to destroy the Duchessa.
这是赫伦和斯图尔特探员
This is Agents Heron and Stewart.
他们是岛上的卧底
They'll be working undercover on the island.
赫伦先生已经在那里定居了
Mr. Heron's already established there,
经营各种生意
running various businesses.
什么生意
What businesses?
赌场酒吧和非法出口
A casino bar, and illegal exports game.
一切有利可图
Profitable?
我们做得很好
I do quite well.
高级纳粹分子是最重要的客户
High-ranking Nazis are my most valued clients.
对你有好处
Good for you.
斯图尔特小姐 演员兼歌手
Miss Stewart, an actress and singer,
在过去的两年 一直和我们一起训练
has been training with us for the last two years.
她将表演
She'll be posing
来自纽约的黄金交易商
as a gold trader from New York.
她的任务是引诱和分散注意力
Her mission is to seduce and distract
目标是该岛指挥官海因里希-鲁尔
the island's Commanding Officer Heinrich Luhr.
她很出色 也有点上进心
She's very capable and somewhat motivated.
何以见得 长官
Motivated how, sir?
我母亲那边是德国犹太人
My mother's side were German Jews.
他们是第一批离开的
They were the first to go.
很遗憾听到这个消息
Very sorry to hear that.
我相信你会康复的
I'm sure you'll recover.
我们还有44天
We have 44 days
在纳粹行动之前
before the Nazis move their operation.
再也不用找他们了
We won't find them again.
如果要做这件事 我需要自己的团队
If I'm to do this, I'll need my own team.
你不会喜欢他们的 他们都是
You won't like them. They're all, uh...
疯子
mad.
我会喜欢的 告诉我他们的名字
They'll need to be. Give us their names.
亨利-海斯
Henry Hayes.
憎恨纳粹 聪明又年轻的爱尔兰人
A smart, young Irishman who hates the Nazis
因为他的哥哥
because his older brother,
是我的好友
who was a close friend of mine,
在一艘U型潜艇击沉他的渔船后 溺水身亡
drowned after a U-boat sank his fishing trawler.
从那时起 我就把他置于我的羽翼之下
I've taken him under my wing ever since.
他狡猾 安静 机智
He's cunning, quiet and wily.
更重要的是
More to the point,
他是个出色的水手 我信任他
Hayes is a magnificent sailor and I trust him.
如果我们要试着击沉一艘大船
If we're going to try and sink a large ship,
我们需要弗莱迪-巴斯 青蛙人
we'll need Freddy "The Buzz" frogman.
他可以双脚并拢游过海峡
He can swim across the channel with his feet tied together.
我承认
Admittedly,
他是个纵火犯 是个可怕的悲惨人物
he's a convicted arsonist and a terrible misery
除非他在破坏什么东西
unless he's destroying something.
但他很擅长把东西炸飞
But he's very good at blowing things up.
接下来 我们需要丹麦锤
Next, we'll need the Danish hammer.
安德斯-拉森
Anders Lassen.
从小与熊摔跤
Grew up wrestling bears
在他的家族庄园里狩猎麋鹿
and hunting elk on his family estate.
他是一个传奇
He's a legend
用一把鲍伊刀和一支弓箭
with a Bowie knife and a bow and arrow.
他18岁离家出走 与纳粹作战
He ran away at 18 to fight the Nazis
在他的兄弟被折磨致死后 他被送进了医院
after the Gestapo tortured his brother to death.
为了给纳粹开膛破肚 他放弃了狩猎
He gave up filleting game for gutting Nazis.
然后 他出现在我们的阵营
He then turned up on our shores
准备与我们并肩作战
ready to fight alongside us.
他是一个无法控制的疯子
He is an uncontrollable mad dog
百窍生烟
who knows a hundred creative ways
内心只有打打杀杀
to kill a man.
最后
And finally,
最重要的是 我们需要杰弗里-阿普利亚德
and most importantly, we'll need Geoffrey Appleyard.
是的 我们知道你会这么想
Yes, we thought you might.
所以我们派他
That's why we sent him
前往费尔南多波执行侦察任务
on a reconnaissance mission to Fernando Po.
不幸的是
Unfortunately,
他在回程时被纳粹抓获
the Nazis nabbed him on his return.
那就更有理由 他知道我们需要知道什么
All the more reason. He knows what we need to know.
他是个策划大师
He's a master planner,
幸存者高手 象棋大师
a master survivor, a chess grand master
和一个拿着刀片的外科医生
and a surgeon with the blade.
我们一起在敦刻尔克的散兵坑里待了两周
We spent two weeks together in a Dunkirk foxhole
如果没有”苹果” 我今天可能还在那里
and if it wasn't for Apple, I would still be there today.
没有”苹果” 就没有使命
No Apple, no mission.
恐怕这是不可能的
I'm afraid that's impossible.
为什么
Why?
因为他被扣押了
Because he's being held
被拉帕尔马岛上的德国驻军击毙
by an entire German garrison on La Palma.
拉帕尔马就快到了
La Palma's on the way.
太疯狂了 你还让我担心
- That's insanity. - You let me worry about that.
我一定要买一件这样的大衣
I must get me one of those coats.
现在 你能不能告诉我们
Now, any chance you can tell us
在这里做什么 长官
what we're doing here, sir?
把你自己擦干 青蛙人 我会告诉你的
Dry yourself off, frogman, and I'll tell you.
好奇心正在吞噬我们所有人 长官
The curiosity is eating us all up, sir.
各位 我对你们的保密工作表示歉意
I apologize for all the secrecy, chaps.
但这是
But this is
一个未经批准 非官方授权的任务
an unsanctioned, unofficial and unauthorized mission.
如果我们被英国人发现
If we're picked up by the Brits,
都会坐牢
we will all go to jail.
如果我们被德国人发现
If we're picked up by the Germans,
就会是酷刑和死亡
torture and death.
那就只有我们四个了
So, it's just the four of us then?
还有亚普莉亚德上尉
And Captain Appleyard.
他负责保护这些信息
He's responsible for securing this information.
然而 他却陷入了困境
He is, however, in a spot of bother.
他被德国人关押在拉帕尔马岛
He is being held by the Germans on La Palma.
我们的首要任务是营救他
Our first job is to liberate him.
哦 就这样 是吗 没了
- Oh, so, that's all, is it? - No.
我们需要确认他的情报
We need to confirm Appleyard's intelligence.
这就是为什么还有两个特工
That's why there are two more agents
就在我们谈话时 正乘火车前往费尔南多波
on their way to Fernando Po by train, as we speak.
到底在做什么
Doing what, exactly?
他们要确保
They'll be ensuring
船上装满了补给品
that those ships are filled with supplies,
所以很值得炸掉它们
so they're worth blowing up in the first place.
占领是一回事
It's one thing taking over the world,
但他们也要接管厨房吗
but do they have to take over the kitchen too?
都是香肠 卷心菜和黑面包
It's all sausage, cabbage and black bread.
你更喜欢哪个
Who would you have preferred?
法国人提供的是精致的古典风格
The French offer the refined classical take.
上等牛排 奶酪 黄油
Cote de boeuf, fromage, le beurre...
足够了
ca suffit!
意大利人的质朴随性又如何
What about the rustic spontaneity of the Italians?
他们的油 扁面条和番茄差点意思
Their oils, the linguine, the tomatoes.
我会跳过扁面条去吃通心粉
I'd climb over the linguine to get to the fettucine.
但是 辛哈雷
But the cinghiale.
嗯
Mmm.
你让我想起了野猪
You have me with the wild boar.
不过 西班牙人的提议
But then again, the Spanish offer
是大杂烩
the smorgasbord
当地的海鲜饭和小吃
of the regional paella and tapas.
还有 安达卢西亚伊比利亚火腿
And Jamon Iberico Andalucia.
所以呢
So?
我们左右为难
We're between a rock and a hard place.
如果英国人赢得了战争
If the Brits win the war,
我们只能吃炸鱼和薯条
we're stuck with fish and chips.
如果德国人赢得了战争
If the Germans win the war,
我们就只能点这个菜单了
we're stuck with this menu.
所以呢
So?
我们会有香肠 卷心菜
We'll have the sausage, the cabbage
和黑面包
and the black bread please.
非常好 谢谢
Tres bien. Merci.
目前的情况
Our situation?
稍等
Steady.
现在
Now.
嗯
Mmm.
我累坏了
I'm exhausted.
请注意些
Entschuldigung, bitte.
停下
Halt!
有问题吗
Is there a problem?
我自己能行 谢谢
I can manage myself, thank you.
我来吧 斯图尔特小姐
Allow me, Miss Stewart.
请吧
Allow me.
谢谢
Thank you.
普罗斯特
Prost!
门
Door.
锁定
Locked.
目前情况
Case?
正在努力
Working on it.
长官 请讲
Sir, contact.
联系方式
Contact.
待命
Standing by.
杜奇莎的清单准备好了吗
Duchessa's manifest. Ready?
准备就绪400枚B级鱼雷 确认
- Ready. - 400 B-grade torpedoes. Check.
400枚B级鱼雷
400 B-grade torpedoes.
确认
Check.
5000吨柴油 确认
5,000 tons of diesel. Check.
5000吨柴油
5,000 tons of diesel.
中尉 什么事 长官
- Lieutenant. - Yes, sir?
确认
Check.
10000个二氧化碳过滤器 确认
10,000 carbon dioxide filters. Check.
斯托克的信息完毕 长官
End of message from Stork, sir.
确认收货
Confirm receipt.
Receipt confirmed.
紧急文件 契克斯
Urgent, Chequers.
把车准备好 通知弗莱明
Get the car ready. Inform Fleming.
收拾一下吧
Let's pack it up.
抢银行没意义
No point robbing the bank
如果金库里没有黄金
if there's no gold in the vault.
谢谢
Thank you.
让人感到欣慰的是
It's truly comforting to know
世界上至少还有一位绅士
there's at least one gentleman in the world.
白痴
Ah! Idiot!
再见
Good day.
香肠 卷心菜和黑面包
Sausage, cabbage and black bread.
希特勒向我们开出了条件
Hitler has made us an offer.
一种绥靖政策
An appeasement.
但我们必须撤军
But we must step down our army,
交出海军 接受纳粹统治
surrender our Navy and accept Nazi rule.
否则 他将
Otherwise, he promises
彻底摧毁英国
total destruction of Britain and her empire.
我们的最佳选择是
Our best option
趁我们还活着 接受希特勒的交易
is to take Hitler's deal while we can.
空军元帅表示同意
The Air Marshal agrees.
他有更多的炸弹 人员 武器
He has more bombs, more men, more machines.
我们坚持不了多久
We won't survive much longer.
你必须做出决定
You have to make the only decision you can make
凭良心说 首相
in good conscience, Prime Minister.
天啊 听听你们自己说的话
Good God, girls. Listen to yourselves.
这不是绥靖政策 而是投降
It's not appeasement, it's surrender.
还是没有意识到对手是谁
You still fail to realize who we're up against.
恕我直言 首相 是您没有意识到这一点
With respect, Prime Minister, it's you who doesn't realize.
我们不能指望打败他
We cannot hope to defeat him.
希特勒是邪恶之人
Hitler is the mainspring of evil,
一个吝啬鬼
a guttersnipe.
不是一个可以与之谈判的人
This is not a man that we can negotiate with.
我读过他的书
I've read his book, Admiral Pound.
他是一个恶毒的 意识形态主义者
The man is a vicious, victimized ideologue.
他不可信
He cannot be trusted.
如果我们可以实现和平
If I thought that we could've achieved peace
通过投降的话
through surrendering,
我早就做了
I'd have done it already.
我要让国家不再妥协
We need to stop our country from starving.
我们需要300万吨物资
We need three million tons of supplies
穿越大西洋
to cross the Atlantic every month.
目前U型潜艇的攻击 使我们损失了其中50%
We are currently losing 50% of that to U-boat attacks.
接受交易的另一个原因
Another reason to take the deal.
我还没说完呢 阿尔吉侬 亲爱的
I've not finished, Algernon, darling.
我们需要美国人
We need the Americans,
他们永远不会参战
and they will never enter the war
如果我们看起来已经是失败的一方
if we already appear to be a losing side.
结束与德国的敌对行动
Ending hostilities with Germany
是摆脱困境的最佳途径
is the best path out of this mess.
我们都同意 首相
We are all in agreement, Prime Minister.
谢谢各位
Thank you, gentlemen.
是的 谢谢你们 先生们
Yes, thank you, gentlemen!
弗莱明 最好是好消息
M, Fleming, this better be good news.
首相
Prime Minister,
我们这里有清单
we have the manifest here, sir.
已经过确认
It's been confirmed
公爵夫人号满载物资
the Duchessa is fully laden with supplies
让U型潜艇无限期地继续作战
to keep the U-boats operational indefinitely.
如果我们要击沉她 正是时候
If we're going to sink her, now is the time.
他们在路上了
They're on their way.
机会呢
And their chances?
如果有人能做到 他们也能做到
Well, if anyone can, they can.
但如果我们被发现
But if we're discovered,
议会将解除您的职务
parliament will remove you from office.
好吧
Well,
我们最好不被发现
we'd better make sure we're not discovered then.
我们将从悬崖边出发
We'll take it from the cliffside.
这是一个85英尺高的陡峭攀岩
It's an 85-foot sheer climb.
没有人会注意到
No one should notice
一艘无害的小渔船
a small, innocuous fishing vessel.
我们将在树林里设点 看会遇到什么
We'll set up in the woods and see what we're up against,
然后再去夜袭
then we'll go for a night raid.
悄悄溜进去 找到苹果 快速出来
Slip in quietly, find Apple, come out fast.
目标数字呢
Numbers?
情报显示 驻军有50至 60 人
Intelligence suggests a garrison of 50 to 60.
每人对付15个
That should be about 15 each.
拉森 别太贪心 你确实名声在外
Lassen, try not to be greedy. You do have a reputation.
我杀人的日子结束了
My killing days are over.
只是作为维和观察员来这里
I'm just here as a peacekeeping observer.
弗雷迪 把工具包起来 全部收起来
Freddy, bag the kit, silence the weapons.
我们什么时候出发
When do we go?
0200.
先攻下塔楼 然后进入无线电室
Take the towers first, then move onto the radio room,
接着军营 最后来到控制室
barracks and end up in the control room...
这里有什么
What do we have here?
纳粹秘密警察
Gestapo.
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
他们越坏 穿得就越好
The badder they are, the better they're dressed.
我真得买一件这样的大衣了
I really must get me one of those coats.
他们一定是为苹果而来
They must be here for Apple.
要么拷问 要么 呃 长官
It's either torture or, uh, extraction, sir.
如果他们把他带走 苹果就完了
If they extract him, it'll be the end of Apple.
我们不会再见到他了
We won't be seeing him again.
恐怕不太好 先生们
I'm afraid, gentlemen,
我们不可能奢望夜晚来临
we're not going to have the luxury of night.
我们得进去了
We're going to have to go in now.
那么 发生了什么
So, what's happened there then?
看起来像
It looks like
它们被射满了箭
they've been plugged full of arrows, Haysey.
那么 箭头去哪儿了
Well, where did the arrows go?
直接穿过去了
Straight through them.
另一边还有两个
There were two more round the other side.
他们现在在哪
Where are they now?
和这边一样
Same place as these two.
纳粹天堂
Nazi heaven.
我们还有不到七分钟的时间
Well, we've got less than seven minutes
以免错过
before they're missed.
警报 狗都是麻烦
Alarms, dogs. None of it good.
潜入内部
Go undercover of the engine.
只有当事情发生时 才能打破掩护
Only break cover when things go bang.
我有个好主意 拉森
I have a great idea, Lassen.
你为什么不自己走呢
Why don't you march off by yourself
让德国人满身是箭
and fill those Germans full of arrows?
弗莱迪 拿起剪刀 把栅栏剪开
Freddy, grab the scissors and help him with that fence.
是 长官
Aye, sir.
跟我来 我们往左走
Haysey, you're with me. We go left.
弗雷迪 拉森 你们右走
Freddy, Lassen, you go right.
先生们 把靴子穿上 祝你们玩得愉快
Fill your boots, gentlemen, and bon appetit.
塔上见
See you at the tower.
请记住 先生们 尽量玩得开心
And remember, gentlemen, try to have fun.
到目前为止 一切顺利
So far, so good.
干得不错
Doing rather well, Haysey.
哦 谢谢
Oh, why thank you, sir.
非常好
It's very good.
看起来不需要躲避了
Sounds like stealth mode's over.
趴下
Haysey, down!
不不
Nein! Nein!
我们认识吗
Do we know each other?
不
No.
那是心脏吗 拉森
Is that a heart, Lassen?
为免生疑
For the avoidance of doubt.
苹果 老伙计
Apple, old boy.
格斯 看来你们见过了
- Gus. - I see you two have met.
我是海斯
This is Haysey.
很荣幸 海斯 是我的荣幸
- Pleasure, Haysey. - Pleasure's mine.
我想你可能需要这些
I thought you might need these.
你想得真周到
Jolly thoughtful of you.
你们都找到他了
You all find him?
哦 太好了
Oh, goody.
该死的 你的奶子怎么了
Bloody hell, what happened to your nipples?
你没事吧
You all right?
你就不能拔掉我的插头吗 电池还开着呢
Couldn't unplug me, could you? Battery's still on.
你看到公爵夫人了吗
Did you see the Duchessa,
拖船吗
the tug boats?
还有很多纳粹士兵
And rather a lot of Nazi soldiers.
为什么你的报告中 没有提到这一点
Why wasn't that in your report?
因为那些士兵和枪
Because those soldiers and those guns,
这些S型潜艇都是新造的
and those S-Boats are all new.
这比期待中的要多得多
That's a lot more than the boys are expecting.
一个月前 有十几名机械师
A month ago, it was a dozen mechanics.
六个醉醺醺的水手
Six drunk sailors.
两个胖西班牙人
Two fat Spaniards.
还有纳粹份子
And a Nazi in a pear tree.
我得说 需要更多的帮助
I'd say, we're gonna need more help.
交给我吧
You leave that to me.
当然
Of course.
但现在
But right now...
你得见见那个人
...you need to meet that man.
你的男人 来这里的原因
Your man. The reason you're here.
啊
Ah.
唯一比纳粹可怕的
The only thing worse than a Nazi...
就是他
is him.
我很失望 赫伦
I'm very disappointed, Heron.
我的仓库里有16个箱子
There are 16 crates in my warehouse
你们尚未运往大陆
you have not yet shipped to the mainland.
不用担心 先生
No need to fret, Herr Luhr.
它们仍会在约定日期前送达
They'll still be delivered by the agreed date.
也许吧
That may be.
但它们占用了宝贵的时间
But they take up valuable space.
为此 我期望
For this, I expect
大幅减少您的费用
a significant reduction in your fee.
我能做到减少5%
I can do 5%...
以示友好
...as a gesture of goodwill.
二十块 别浪费我宝贵的时间讨价还价了
Twenty. And don't waste my precious time haggling.
严格来说
Well, strictly speaking,
不应减少
there should be no reductions,
因为还没有任何违约行为
since there's not yet been any breach of contract.
5个字 已经很客气 20个字 就像酸溜溜的音符
Five is more than polite, 20 rings like a sour note,
那些罐子
it jars.
会结冰
It jars?
我被指责不友好吗
Am I being accused of disharmony?
我认为这是对我个人的侮辱
I take that as a personal affront.
我猜你不是秘书
And I am supposing you are not the secretary.
斯图尔特小姐 我说过要安排的联系人
Miss Stewart is the contact I said I'd arrange.
啊 你的纽约黄金联系人
Ah, your New York gold contact?
我告诉过你
I told you,
我已经有了满意的安排
I already have a satisfying arrangement.
请坐
Have a seat.
谢谢
Thank you.
希望我不会让你失望
Well, I hope I don't disappoint.
我无法就这次交谈做出决定
I can't make a decision on this presentation.
早点的话
Early days.
好吧 如果来得太早的话
Well, if early days do come too soon,
猎人之月 四季更迭
and seasons change with a Hunter's Moon.
嗯
Hmm.
我不得不说
I have to say, Heron,
你所有的缺点
for all your flaws,
确实有从帽子里掏兔子的习惯
you do have a habit of pulling rabbits from hats.
那么 你想转移多少黄金呢
So, how much gold do you wish to move,
斯图尔特小姐
Miss Stewart?
有多少是多少
As much as you can find.
正如我之前提到的
As I mentioned before,
已经有一个非常有利可图的安排
I do already have a very profitable arrangement.
尽管有你的说法
And despite of your commentary,
我为自己能保持冷静而自豪
I pride myself on maintaining harmony.
我为什么要招待你
Now, why should I entertain you?
因为你会赚更多的钱 享受更多的乐趣
Because you'll make more money and have lots of fun
与此同时
whilst doing so.
如果我说话不算数 无需给钱
If I'm not good for my word, don't pay me.
好样的
Bravo.
我会和他们谈谈 再会
I will talk to my people and then we'll rendezvous.
真可爱
Lovely.
当狡猾的红猫在黎明吠叫时
When the sly red cat barks at dawn,
杀人只为取乐
and kills just for her pleasure,
猫偷吃的饭菜由谁分享
who shares the meal the cat did steal
当两个人都看得津津有味时
when both looked on in pleasure?
再见
Auf wiedersehen.
谜语是一个很好的点子
The riddle was a nice touch.
上钩了
The hook's in.
现在要小心把他卷进来
Now be careful how you reel him in.
我会确保港口空无一人
I'll make sure the harbor's empty
当他们到达时
when the boys arrive.
你打算怎么做
How are you going to do that?
我会在俱乐部举办一个派对
I'll throw a party at my club.
军官舞会
A costume party for the officers
并在码头为士兵们举行了第二次聚会
and a second party at the dock for the soldiers.
人们喜欢我的派对
People like my parties.
除了鲁尔
Everyone but Luhr.
这是你的工作
That will be your job.
所有的老鼠都会跟着吹笛者走
All the rats will follow the piper.
所以 如果我理解正确的话
So, if I understand correctly,
现在在拉帕尔马
we're currently here in La Palma.
我们将环绕德国控制的非洲航行
We'll sail around German-controlled Africa
到费尔南多波
to Fernando Po,
它位于赤道以北
which is just north of the Equator,
在西非海岸附近
just off the West African coast.
这是最短的路线
So that's the shortest route?
是的 但我们不想走得太快
Yes, but we don't want to go shorter.
我们的首要任务是不被发现
Our priority is not to be seen.
你是说 被人发现
You mean, be seen again.
又来了 现在有点马虎了
Again? Getting a little sloppy on us now, Gussy?
已经交谈过了
Had a run-in already?
别管我们 苹果 老伙计
Never mind us, Apple, old boy.
再次提醒
Remind me again
你是怎么发现自己的乳头连着汽车电池
how you found your nipples attached to a car battery.
是的 不是我的错
Yes. Wasn't my fault.
智力低下 另外 这几乎是值得的
Bad intelligence. Plus it was almost worth it
观看 捕心者 的工作
to watch the heart-snatcher at work.
与其说我是个战士 不如说我是个情人
I'm better known as a lover than a fighter.
天哪
Jesus Christ!
如果这就是你的战斗方式 我真不想看到
If that's how you fight, I'd hate to see you love.
你不必担心这个
You don't have to worry about that,
你对我来说太漂亮了
you're too pretty for me.
而弗雷迪
Freddy, on the other hand...
你得先抓住我
You'd have to catch me first.
我确实喜欢打猎
I do love to hunt.
你会很幸运的
You'd be lucky.
我真的越来越热了
I'm really getting quite hot.
总之 建议是 走这条更宽广的道路
Anyway, my suggestion is that we take this wider route.
显然更长
It's obviously longer
但应避免危机
but it should avoid any awkward conversations
德国U型潜艇或英国军舰
with German U-boats or British warships.
视天气而定
Weather-dependent,
我们应该在15天内到达那里
we should make it there in 15 days.
同意
Agreed.
海斯 你觉得能做到吗
Haysey, do you think you could manage that?
交给我吧 长官
Leave it to me, sir.
照我说的做
Just do as you're told
再给我倒一杯
and get me another drink!
上尉 长官
Captain, sir.
要吃点什么吗
Can I get you something to eat?
我可以 这边请
May I... Come this way.
把你的手拿开
Take your hands off me.
你知道的
You know,
我喜欢你 费米
I like you, Femi.
但你要是再碰我一下 就得进监狱
But you touch me again and you're going to jail.
费米
Femi.
我来吧
I'll deal with him.
请照顾好斯图尔特小姐
Please take care of Miss Stewart.
你知道需要什么吗 比尼亚上尉
You know what you need, Captain Binea?
我知道我需要什么
I know what I need.
但是你呢 里卡多
But do you, Ricardo?
你得再喝一杯
You need another drink.
马蒂
Marty,
好东西
good stuff.
里卡多 这就是我爱你的原因
Ricardo, that's why I love you.
你懂的
You understand.
这里是费尔南多波
This is Fernando Po.
欢迎大家
Everybody's welcome.
嗯 大家
Si... Everybody.
我觉得人太多了
Too many body I think.
阿曼多
Armando?
你和我们的新朋友闹翻了吗
Have you fallen out with our new friends?
这不公平 里卡多
It's not fair, Ricardo.
这是我的港湾
This is my harbor.
我说了算
I am in charge.
他们踩到你的脚趾了吗
Are they stepping on your toes?
它们不踩踏 而是踩踏
They don't step, they stamp!
他们什么也没告诉比尼亚队长
They tell Captain Binea nothing.
现在我才知道
Only now do I hear
公爵夫人号提前离港
the Duchessa is leaving the harbor early.
很好 做得好
Well, good riddance.
海港将再次属于你
The harbor will be yours again.
你什么时候才能摆脱那个丑陋的家伙
When will you be free of that ugly vessel?
三天前
Three days earlier.
那我们应该再喝一杯
Then we should have another drink.
庆祝 马蒂
To celebrate. Marty...
为我们的港务局首长再来一次
Another round for our Harbor Master.
那么 上尉 你知道他们想搬到哪里去吗
So, Captain, do you know where they wish to relocate?
杀人取乐的既不是猫 也不是狗
It's neither cat nor dog that kills for fun,
是狐狸精 不是别人
it's the vixen, not another.
只有两个人 以杀人为乐
There's only two that kill for fun,
我漂亮的朋友
my pretty friend,
狐狸和他的人类兄弟
the fox and his human brother.
我相信已经解开了你的小谜题
I believe I have resolved your little riddle.
干杯 做得好
Chapeau. You play well.
说到狐狸
Speaking of foxes,
霍洛维茨和梅耶 西街47
Horowitz and Meyer, West 47th Street.
你听说过他们吗
Have you heard of them?
我想没有 没有
I don't believe I have, no.
他们是最大的黄金交易商
They're the largest gold traders
在纽约城
in Midtown New York
你却没听说过他们
and you haven't heard of them?
恐怕没有
I'm afraid I haven't, no.
我当然熟悉霍洛维茨和哈伊姆
I am familiar, of course, with Horowitz and Haim.
但他们在城市的西边
But they're in the west side of the city.
不过话说回来
But then again,
我相信你已经知道了 不是吗
I'm sure you already knew that, didn't you?
我很好奇
I'm curious,
您觉得如何与犹太人打交道
how do you find dealing with the Jew?
哦 天哪
Oh, dear.
我从一个陷阱中滑落
I've slipped from one snare
却发现自己身处另一个世界
only to find myself in another.
我该怎么说呢
How shall I put this?
我担心你们杰出的领导人
I fear your brilliant leader
对古代雅胡达部落的描述有误
has mischaracterized the ancient tribe of Jahuda.
他们不仅能够
Their ability to not only
脖子上套着一只靴子 也能活3000 年
survive 3,000 years with a boot on their neck,
但尽管如此 也会繁荣昌盛
but to prosper in spite of it...
我怀疑激发了他内心中撒旦般的嫉妒
I suspect it inspired satanic jealousy within him.
总之
In conclusion,
看样子
it looks as though
这位女士懂得太多了
the lady doth protest too much.
亵渎神明的蛋糕上还有樱桃吗
Is there a cherry to go on this blasphemous cake,
还是你已经完成了
or have you finished?
我必须承认
I must confess,
我不仅尊敬和钦佩犹太人
not only do I respect and admire the Jew...
我就是
I am one.
开个玩笑
Kidding!
他们是贪婪的老鼠
They're greedy rats.
我认为这可能是
I think this could be
一段美好友谊的开始
the beginning of a beautiful friendship.
那就开个派对庆祝一下
Then I shall throw a party to celebrate.
我不喜欢派对
I don't care for parties.
哦 扫兴鬼 大家都喜欢派对
Oh, spoilsport! Everybody loves a party.
公爵夫人离开了
The Duchessa's leaving
比我们想象的早了三天
three days earlier than we thought.
如果我们不告诉他们
If we don't tell the Maid Honor,
会来得太晚
they'll arrive too late.
来了
Incoming.
联系中
Contact.
岛上的杰里人比预期的要多
More Jerries on the island than expected.
储藏室里的罐装腌牛肉
Tin of corned beef's out of pantry
提前三天到达
three days early.
我要这个
I'll take that.
这是机密 长官 只对M保密
It's confidential, sir. For M only.
在进行破译时
When it comes to make the extraction,
它必须是一个非常
it needs to be a very...
长官 有留言
Sir. Message, sir.
岛上的杰里人比预期的要多
More Jerries on the island than expected.
腌牛肉从储藏室里拿出来了
Corned beef's out of the pantry
提前三天
three days early.
走快点
Move faster.
是的 但该地区发现的U型潜艇越来越多
Yes, but there's increased U-boat sightings in the area.
长官
Sir.
任务还在继续
The mission's still proceeding.
所以 岛上有更多的士兵
So, there's more soldiers on the island
船会提前出发吗
and the boat's leaving earlier?
是的
Yes.
那么 我们如何才能走得更快
Well, how are we meant to move faster?
我们不能再快了
We can't move faster.
我们正以最快的速度前进
We're going as fast as we can.
这是一艘渔船 不是快艇
This is a fishing boat, it's not a speedboat.
首相
Prime Minister,
公爵夫人将在12天后离开费尔南多波
the Duchessa's leaving Fernando Po in 12 days.
我们目前的日程安排是
On our current schedule,
他们会晚到三天
they'll arrive three days too late.
还能这样做吗
Can it still be done?
我们仍在等待答复
We're still awaiting a response
来自菲利普斯少校
from Major Phillips.
如果我们不能走得更快 那就要换短路线
If we can't move faster, we'll go shorter.
我们可以在12天内到达费尔南多波
We can get to Fernando Po in 12 days.
等等 你说我们不能走这条路线
Hold on, you said we couldn't go shorter.
不 我说我们不想走得太危险
No, I said we don't want to go shorter.
我们会被U型潜艇击沉
He said we'll get mowed down by a U-boat.
或者更糟的是 被英国人抓走
Or worse, picked up by the Brits.
他们的驱逐舰队正在穿过那里
Their armada of destroyers are crossing there.
我们将在U型潜艇上方航行
We will literally be sailing over U-boats.
对不起 伙计们 我们走得比较危险
Sorry, lads, we go shorter.
三 二 一
Drei, zwei, eins...
先生们 我想说
Gentlemen, as I speak to you now,
再次来到伦敦
London once again
在纳粹从天而降的攻击下瑟瑟发抖
shudders beneath a Nazi onslaught from the skies.
在这种时候
And at such times,
人们的内心被激起责任感
the hearts of men are stirred to duty.
但你们不是那样的人
But you are not such men.
你没有被选中
You were not chosen
为您的显赫荣誉或崇高理想
for your conspicuous honor or high ideals.
如果你被选中
You were chosen
因为你是最后一击
because you are the last resort.
赋予你们的使命
The mission you have been given
这是前所未有的
is of a sort never before undertaken.
需要冷酷无情的人 毫不犹豫的人
It demands ruthless men, who will not hesitate
屈从于战争惯例
to stoop beneath the conventions of war.
手中握有鲜血的人
Men who do not keep clean hands.
像你这样的人
Men like you.
然而 谁还在密谋
And yet, who still conspire
在不和谐的言语中
in their own discordant harmony.
他们知道自己一去不复返 却毫不在意
Who know and yet do not care that they may never return.
不为荣耀而前进的人
And who press onward not for glory,
或为职责 或为他人
or for duty, or for me,
但因为你们 是永不停息的人
but because you are men who will not stop
直到完成战斗为止
until it is done.
祝你们一路顺风 先生们
Godspeed, gentlemen.
呃
Uh... Chaps...
那是一艘英国驱逐舰
That's a British destroyer.
我们该走了
We should move.
我们无法避开的 长官
We can't outrun that, sir.
我们见过他 他也见过我们
Well, we've seen them, they've seen us.
坚持住
Hold fast, Maid Honor.
我们正在准备登船队伍
We're preparing a boarding party.
你好 船长
Hello, Captain!
没什么令人兴奋的
Nothing exciting here.
我们只是瑞典渔民
We're just Swedish fishermen.
上前 约根森
Step forward, Jorgensen!
约根森 你是瑞典人
Jorgensen, you're Swedish.
问问他们要去哪里 好吗
Ask them where they're heading, would you?
不是你 拉森
Not you, Lassen.
呃
Uh...
我想听听马奇菲利普斯的意见
I want to hear March-Phillips have a go.
啊
Ah.
有道理
Fair enough.
游戏开始了 指挥官
Game's up, Commander.
不能责怪一个女孩的努力
Can't blame a girl for trying.
干得好 少校
Good effort, Major.
但恐怕你得跟我们走一趟
But I'm afraid you are going to have to come with us.
请问
May I ask under whose authority
我们被劫持了吗
we've been waylaid?
奉庞德上将之命
On the orders of Admiral Pound.
中尉
First Lieutenant.
您正在追击
You are pursuing
不法犯罪团伙
an unsanctioned criminal enterprise
在国际水域
in international waters.
会引起一场混乱
You're going to cause an upset.
我想已经有点不高兴了 指挥官
I think we're a little past upset, Commander.
史蒂文斯 你有什么发现
Stevens, what have you got?
我听到了乒乒乓乓的声音 长官
I had a ping, sir.
贪婪的小纳粹
The greedy little Nazi
不会满足于控制欧洲大部分地区
won't be satisfied with holding most of Europe,
他的目标是我们的绿色宜人之地
he's after our own green and pleasant land.
谢天谢地 你来了
Well, thank God you're here
带着你的小木头战舰
with your little wooden battleship
和你的五人军队
and your five-man army.
U型潜艇方位 273
U-boat, bearing 273.
敲响警钟
Sound the alarm.
上船吧
Come aboard.
U型潜艇接近中右舷 长官
U-boat approaching. Starboard side, sir.
战斗就位
Battle stations!
少校 也是为了你好
Major, if you know what's good for you,
回去吧 很好 指挥官
- you'll head home. - Very good, Commander.
海斯 让我们远离鱼雷磁铁
Haysey, get us away from that torpedo magnet
尽快
as quickly as possible.
是 长官 苹果 去船尾
Aye, sir. Apple, man the stern.
弗雷迪 在主帆上
Freddy, on the main sail.
拉森到船头去 解开站台
Lassen to the bow, now. Untie that station!
是
Aye.
快点 伙计们
Quickly now, lads!
为我们升起前帆 好吗 伙计们
Hoist that foresail for us, will you, boys?
主帆准备就绪
Main sail ready to haul!
好了 弗雷迪 现在升起主帆
All right, Freddy, now raise that main sail!
是
Aye.
警告声
Report sounding.
轴承163.
Bearing 163.
拉森 修整主帆
Lassen, trim the main sail
然后打结
and then tie it off!
你怎么能指望好呢
How do you expect good?
警告声
Report sounding.
轴承115.
Bearing 115.
发射深水炸弹
Fire depth charges.
这就是你要找的人么
So, this is your man that gets things done?
他的名字叫坎普比利  带 "K"
His name is Kamp Billy... with a K.
他上的是英国寄宿学校
And he went to an English boarding school?
不是普通的寄宿学校 是伊顿公学
Not just any boarding school. He went to Eton,
寄宿学校
the boarding school.
对
Right...
他在这里做什么
Then what's he doing here?
他是个王子
He's a prince.
究竟是什么王子
A prince of what, exactly?
费尔南多波王子
The Prince of Fernando Po!
这么说 他既是海盗 又是贵族
So, he's part pirate, part aristocrat?
真别致
Chic.
他也是我们解决方案的一部分
He's also a part of our solution.
RH.
KB.
他回来了
He's back in town.
老大
Chief.
看来你总是带着礼物来
Seems like you always come bearing gifts.
她适合我吗
Is she for me?
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
我不适合你
I'm not for you,
但这些适合
but these are.
嗯 好东西 美味
Mmm. Goodies. Yummy.
阿德 主任
- Ade... - Chief.
来吧 来吧
Come on, come on.
有人很有品味
Someone has taste.
比母鸡的牙齿还稀有
Rarer than hens' teeth.
RH 告诉我 KB
Well, RH tells me that KB
是唯一可以交谈的人
is the only man to talk to
在完成任务时
when it comes to getting things done.
为什么我觉得自己
Why do I feel like I've gone from being
从捕食者对猎物
the predator to the prey?
年轻的女士 你的入场式真不错
Quite an entrance, young lady.
条件是我们要对它们进行抽样检查
It's on the condition that we sample them...
现在
now.
阿德 摆好桌子
Ade, set the table.
好的 老大
Chief.
然后公爵说
And then the Duke said,
"推进去 直到它停下来 "
"Push it in till it stops!"
你真是个武器高手
You are quite the weapon.
我想是的
I was right,
我是猎物
I was the prey.
我会帮你 因为我不喜欢纳粹
I'll help you because I don't like Nazis.
不是因为他们是纳粹 而是因为他们很俗气
Not because they're Nazis but because they're gauche.
我再帮一把 给你12个最好的手下
I'll give you a tug and 12 of my best men,
包括你本人
including yours truly.
但如果我要帮你 谁来帮我
But if I'm gonna help you, who's gonna help me?
因为你不是士兵 RH
Because you're not a soldier, RH.
不 但她是
No, but she is.
她会把你的人打得落花流水
She'll outshoot your best man.
我告诉过你
I told you.
不  不 不
- No! - No!
鹳鸟送货 确认
Stork delivery. Check.
确认
Check.
23个男孩 确认
Twenty-three boys. Check.
鹳鸟送货
Stork delivery.
23个男孩
Twenty-three boys.
17个女孩
Seventeen girls.
集合地点 费尔南多波外20公里处
Meeting point 20 kilometers outside Fernando Po.
与赫伦会合
The rendezvous with Heron.
你能带我们过去吗
Can you get us there?
如果天气晴朗
If the weather holds,
我可以的 长官
I can, sir.
20英镑赌这不会有好结果
Twenty quid says this doesn't end well.
为了谁
For who?
对他们来说
For them.
你不能拿自己当赌注 那是假球
You can't bet on yourself, Haysey. That's match-fixing.
开始吧
Let's do it.
苍鹭 好久不见
Heron, it's been too long.
很高兴见到你 格斯
Good to see you, Gus.
苹果
Apple.
这是坎普比利 费尔南多波王子
This is Kamp Billy, the Prince of Fernando Po.
殿下
Your Highness.
他同意帮助我们
He's agreed to help us.
请原谅我 但是
Forgive me, but...
我有一种奇怪的感觉 我们以前见过
I have a peculiar feeling that we've met before.
我经常遇到这种情况 我的旅行经历非常丰富
I get that a lot. I'm extremely well-traveled.
不 不 这是一种特殊的感觉
No, no. It's a particular sense.
我想你没打过板球吧
I don't suppose you played cricket, did you?
伊顿公学上尉 21岁至22岁
Captained Eton. '21 to '22.
我就知道 我认得你的脸
I knew I knew your face!
就在奖杯柜旁边
Right next to the trophy cabinet.
八英尺高的巨幅肖像
An eight-foot-tall huge portrait.
是的 正是如此
Yes, exactly that!
一只眼睛盯着边界
One eye on the boundary...
一只眼睛盯着酒馆
...one eye on the pub.
很高兴你能加入我们
Bloody glad to have you aboard.
很高兴来到这里 老伙计
Bloody good to be here, old boy.
真无聊
I'm very bored
这些纳粹分子为非作歹
with these Nazis making a nuisance of themselves.
我是说 这对生意很不利
I mean, it's terrible for business.
我非常高兴
I'm only too pleased
帮你能让他们吃点苦头
to help you serve them a bloody nose.
这种态度值得称赞
That's a commendable attitude.
那么 你有什么计划
So, what's your plan?
苹果
Apple.
我们要击沉公爵夫人号
We're going to sink the Duchessa,
加上两艘拖船
plus the two tugs.
削弱希特勒的大西洋U艇舰队
Crippling Hitler's Atlantic fleet of U-boats.
非常好
Very good.
问题是 我们的老朋友纳粹
The thing is, our old friends the Nazis
并不简单
aren't making it the easiest.
我们的人数是二百比五
We're outnumbered two hundred to five.
士兵比我们预计的要多一些
There's a few more soldiers than we anticipated.
我认为要
I think that we're gonna have
再找几个魁梧的小伙子
to find ourselves a few more strapping lads.
阿德
Ade...
对
Right...
是的 我想这样就可以了
Yes, I think that will do.
我们带了一些武器 如果你需要的话
We brought some weapons if you need.
你们留着吧 我们自己带了
You hold onto those. We brought our own.
给他们看看家伙
Oyah! Show them the iron!
真牛逼
Marvelous.
你知道公爵夫人号
You do know the Duchessa is
距离港口一侧是否超过200英尺
more than 200 feet from the harbor side?
而她就在灯光的照耀下
And she's in full glare of the lights.
不容易沉下去
She's not gonna be easy to sink
别引起不必要的注意
without attracting unwanted attention.
是的 这就是为什么赫伦会安装炸弹的原因
Yes. That's why Heron will plant a bomb
在我们划船进港之前 先把灯吹灭
to blow the lights, before we paddle in
并在船体上安装炸药
and rig the hull with explosives.
到炸药引爆时
By the time the explosives detonate,
我们早已离开
we'll be heading home.
如果按照我的方式 一枪都不用开
If I had it my way, a shot'll never be fired.
你又有多少次 按自己的方式行事
And how often do you have it your way?
那要看你问谁了 老伙计
Depends on who you ask, old boy.
先生们
Gentlemen...
老大
- Ade. - Chief.
让他们做好准备
Prepare the men.
你准备好了 我就拿走那20块 弗雷迪
I'll take that 20 whenever you're ready, Freddy.
公爵夫人明天早上就会离开
The Duchessa will be gone by the morning.
你能做到吗
Can you manage that?
这是两根电线和滴答声
It's two wires and a tick-tock.
我肯定能应付
I'm sure I can cope.
你该担心的不是我
It's not me you should be worried about.
我从没带过纳粹去参加派对
I've never taken a Nazi to a party.
只要别参加他的派对就行
Just don't end up at one of his parties.
别担心我
Don't worry about me.
我要开个自己的小派对
I'm gonna have my own little party.
为伙计们干杯 为国王陛下的政府干杯
Drink for the boys, on His Majesty's government.
通常 我会咬掉你的手
Ordinarily, I'd bite your hand off,
因为众所周知 我喜欢一磅纸币
as I have been known to love a pound note.
但这次
But on this occasion,
我请客
the drinks are on me.
然而
However,
如果国王陛下的政府正在发放头衔
if His Majesty's government was handing out titles...
你已经是王子了 老伙计
You're already a prince, old boy.
有费尔南多波王子 但
There's Prince of Fernando Po, but...
王国骑士有一定的古老性
a Knight of the Realm has a certain antiquity to it.
起来 坎普比利爵士
Arise, Sir Kamp Billy.
你是个好人 格斯
You're a good man, Gus.
祝你好运 比利
Good luck, Billy.
你好
Hola!
早上好 先生们
Buenas tardes, companeros!
先生 有人找您
My Herr, you have a visitor.
哒哒哒
Ta-da!
埃及艳后需要她的凯撒
Cleopatra needs her Caesar.
穿上它
Put it on.
谢谢你 蒂莫西
Thank you, Timothy.
等一下
One second.
蒂莫西
Timothy...
我有一个打算
I have a counter offer.
让我们先把打扮放在一边
Let's put this dressing up aside.
这是为孩子们准备的 而我们不是孩子
It's for children. And we are not children.
让我们打造自己的派对
Let's make our own party.
黑暗派对
A dark party.
黑暗的纳粹党
A dark Nazi party.
有音乐和英俊的纳粹
With music, lubrication and a handsome Nazi.
自从我来到这里
Since I've been here,
我曾被恶毒的东西咬过
I've been bitten by things that croak and slither,
蝎子在我的靴子里筑巢 我无法入睡
scorpions nest in my boots and I can't sleep
丛林中的无情嚎叫声
for the relentless howl of jungle entropy.
今晚
Tonight,
我要去那个派对 你要带我去
I'm going to that party, and you are taking me.
现在 穿上它
Now, put it on.
哦
Oh.
很好
Very well.
啊 你好
Ah! Hola!
灯光熄灭时 我们会行动
We move when the lights go out.
好吧 里卡多
All right, Ricardo,
今天你是 埃尔卡皮坦
today you're El Capitan.
阿曼多 酒吧是你的了
Armando, the bar is yours.
享用它 玩得开心
Use it. Abuse it at your will.
这就是我爱你的原因
That's why I love you.
跟我来 帅哥
Come with me, handsome.
我需要你让男人们开心
I need you to keep the men happy.
要多开心
How happy?
嗯
Mmm.
老鼠进窝了吗
Are the rats in the nest?
你找不到德国 西班牙或意大利军官
You won't find a German, Spanish or Italian officer
今晚在其他任何地方
anywhere else tonight.
在海港啤酒节之间
Between the beer fest at the harbor
和这次小聚
and this little get-together,
这将使90%的士兵远离码头
that'll be 90% of the soldiers away from the dock.
冲锋号准备炸毁港口灯
The charge is set to blow the harbor lights
在30分钟内
in 30 minutes.
你能让他在这里待那么久吗
Can you keep him here that long?
傻孩子 傻问题 看看这身服饰
Silly boy, silly question. Look at the dress.
你好
Hi.
这也叫派对
So, you call this a party?
这只是冰山一角
This is just the thin end of the wedge.
我为你量身打造了一场演出
I've created a performance just for you.
好吧 我可以给你看一个真正的派对
Well, I could show you a real party.
我为什么要在乎 意大利面
Why do I care, Spaghetti?
披萨
Pizza.
对不起 我得去补补妆了
Excuse me while I powder my nose.
又怎么了
What, again?
别慌 凯撒 好好学你的意大利语
Don't panic, Caesar. Brush up on your Italian.
您的礼物需要靓丽
Your gift needs to be wrapped.
请让那些警官继续喝酒
Keep those officers drinking, please.
当然 好的 谢谢你 费米
- Of course. Okay. - Thank you, Femi.
公爵夫人号的船体已经加固
The Duchessa's hull has been reinforced.
它不会沉下去
It won't sink.
我们必须停止任务
We need to stop the mission.
这很难做到
That's going to be hard to do.
听我说
Listen to me.
我们的任务将会失败
Our mission will fail.
炸药不起作用
The explosives won't work
因为船体加强加固
because he's reinforced it to be unsinkable.
你必须马上阻止他们
You have to stop them now.
但是 冲锋号就要爆炸了
But the charge is about to blow the lights.
好吧 如果你不能让灯熄灭
Well, if you can't stop the lights,
请阻止他们
stop the men.
鲁尔绝不能离开派对
Luhr must not leave this party.
我会让他忙起来的 走吧
I'll keep him busy. Go, now.
我们出发了
And we're off.
格斯 等等
Gus, wait.
鹳呼叫女仆 鹳呼叫女仆 请回答
Stork to Maid, Stork to Maid, come in.
第五频道
Channel five.
我是女仆 切换到20
This is Maid. Switching to 20.
说吧
Go ahead.
罐头牛肉无法敲碎
Tin of corned beef can't be cracked.
船无法击沉
The ship cannot be sunk.
炸药会失效
Explosives will fail.
是斯托克 长官
It's Stork, sir.
让他开免提
Put him on open speaker.
粟米牛肉不能开裂
Corned beef can't be cracked.
斯托克 这是M
Stork, this is M.
别管什么腌牛肉了 想办法吧
Never mind the corned beef. Just find a way.
庞德来了 长官
- Over. - Pound incoming, sir.
回复 把它关掉
- Repeat... - Switch that off.
我们必须
We must...
立即停止
Stop this immediately.
你现在所做的一切到此为止
What you are doing ends now,
否则你们每一个人都将受到法庭的审判
or every last one of you will be subject to a tribunal.
清楚了吗
Is that clear?
我不知道你在说什么 长官
I don't know what you're talking about, sir.
是这样吗 中士
Is that correct, Sergeant?
保持联系
Hold position.
还要多久 斯托克
How long, Stork?
等待命令 给我
- Awaiting orders. - Give me that.
待命
Stand by.
马奇 菲利普斯
March-Phillips,
这是庞德上将给你的直接命令
this is Admiral Pound giving you a direct order.
立即取消任务
Abort this mission now.
我相信
I will make sure that
你们谁也别想再重见天日
none of you see the light of day again.
你们将度过余生
You will spend the rest of your lives
陛下高兴时就把他们关起来
locked up at His Majesty's pleasure.
包括你们所有人
That includes all of you.
杰弗里 阿普利亚德
Geoffrey Appleyard,
安德斯 拉森
Anders Lassen,
弗雷迪 巴兹 抱歉
- Freddy Buzz... - I'm sorry...
和亨利 海斯
...and Henry Hayes.
听不清楚
Can't quite make out
你在说什么
what you're saying.
再见
Bye.
清楚了吗
Is... Is that clear?
什么 什么
Sorry? What?
不 我听不太清楚
I can't... I can't quite hear you.
麻烦 滚开
Please... fuck off.
你的行动太鲁莽了 旅长
You and your operation are reckless, Brigadier.
我将亲自向议会提议
I will personally advise parliament
要求解除首相职务
to have the Prime Minister removed from office.
我要让你关门大吉
And I am going to shut you down.
收到 清楚了 长官
Message received loud and clear, sir.
我建议你也滚开 中士
I suggest you also fuck off, Sergeant.
弗莱明 联系马奇 菲利普斯
Fleming, contact March-Phillips.
给我接首相热线
Lily, get me the Prime Minister on hotline.
马上 先生 01号
- Right away, sir. - Come in, 01.
你接通了吗
Come in, do you receive?
什么事 首相
- Yes? - Prime Minister,
恐怕我们被发现了
I'm afraid we've been discovered.
我们中间有内鬼
There was a mole in our midst
庞德上将
and Admiral Pound
已下令中止任务
has ordered the mission to be aborted.
他想让议会解除你的职务
He wants to have parliament remove you from office.
任务必须继续
The mission must continue.
01 这里是基地 完毕
01, this is base. Over.
如果庞德有问题 告诉他
Tell Pound if he has a problem,
他知道我在哪里
to take it up with me. He knows where I live.
告诉大家 继续前进
Tell the men to press on.
恐怕我们失去了联系 长官
I'm afraid we've lost all communication, sir.
我们一定能做些什么
There must be something that we can do.
我唯一能做的就是提醒你
The only thing I can do is remind you,
我们选择马奇 菲利普斯的原因
the reason we chose March-Phillips
是因为他不服从命令
is because he doesn't follow orders.
希望我们的选择没错
Then let's hope we chose well.
公爵夫人号的船体已经加固
The Duchessa's hull has been reinforced.
并不意味着不能击沉
Which means she can't be sunk.
至少以我们携带的炸药数量 确实如此
At least not with the amount of explosives we're carrying.
我想知道到底发生了什么 什么情况
Just wondering how and when exactly this took place.
无论如何 都不重要了 重要的是已经发生了
It's not important how and when, it's happened.
这很重要
Well, it is kind of important, Gus.
我不在乎坐牢
I don't care about the prison time,
但我关心的是完成我们的任务
but I do care about finishing what we've started.
谢谢你 弗雷迪
Thank you, Freddy.
一定是搞错了
There must be some sort of mistake.
不可能只是加强
You can't just reinforce...
没有错 海斯
There's no mistake, Haysey.
只是不知道具体的加固方式
I'm just lost about how and when exactly...
够了
Enough!
我们为什么不击沉拖船
Why don't we sink the tug boats?
中断U型潜艇的补给
Get rid of the shuttle to the U-boats.
这还不够
It's not enough.
他们会在一周内更换
They'll replace them in a week.
我们为什么不偷呢
Why don't we steal them?
我们可以用比利的船
We can use Billy's boat
将公爵夫人号拖出港口
to drag the Duchessa out of the harbor
并偷走另外两艘德国拖船
and steal the other two German tug boats
为U型潜艇提供服务
that service the U-boats.
我们该怎么做呢
And how are we supposed to do that?
她不仅是双层的 重量也是原来的两倍
Not only is she double-plated, weighing twice as much,
但你需要船员 移动这么大的一艘船
but you'd need a full crew to move a ship that size.
拖船就是船员
The tug boats are the crew.
我们把杜奇萨拖到海边
We tow the Duchessa out to the ocean
而且 还能偷走很多东西
and, well, steal the lot.
然后呢 我们还是不能击沉他们
Then what? We still can't sink them.
我们不需要
We don't need to.
我们驶入国际水域
We sail into international waters
并将一切移交给海军
and hand everything over to the Navy.
反正他们也在跟踪我们
They're following us anyway,
所以他们会非常高兴见到我们
so they'll be more than happy to see us again.
那么锚呢
And what about the anchor?
你看到它的大小了吗
Have you seen the size of it?
如果我们真的要移动它
If we're gonna actually start to move her,
他们的S艇会在几秒钟内追上我们
their S-boats will catch us in seconds.
那么 你打算怎么做
Well, what are you going to do
你带了那么多炸药 弗雷迪
with all the explosives you brought, Freddy?
我们用它们来炸锚
We'll use them to blow the anchor.
我们会给S型艇装上设备 让他们跟不上
We'll rig the S-boats so they can't follow,
钻机为U型潜艇提供燃料储备
rig the fuel reserve that supplies the U-boats,
然后 好吧 炸掉这一切
and then, well, blow the lot up.
燃料爆炸会
That fuel explosion's gonna bring
把每个人都炸到地下
everyone and their mother down to the harbor.
我们设置了导火索
We set the fuse,
这样 一旦我们离开港口 卸油装置就会爆炸
so that the fuel dump blows once we're outside the harbor.
然后我们悄悄溜出去
Then we sneak out quietly.
不错
Not bad.
这是耍小聪明
It's very greedy.
我加入好吧
- Well, I'm in. - Well,
我不会走的 除非我有一颗纳粹之心
I'm not leaving until I have a barrel full of Nazi hearts.
你让我做什么 我就做什么 长官
I'll do whatever you tell me to do, sir.
先生们
Gentlemen,
我们去偷几艘船吧
let's steal some boats.
结果发现是双层的 所以计划有变
Turns out she's double-plated, so change of plans.
我们要去偷船
We're going to steal the boats instead.
这可能吗
Is that even possible?
我不太确定
I'm not entirely sure.
如果你愿意 我们也愿意
But if you're up for it, so are we.
你知道这意味着什么
And you know what that means.
血流得更多 汗流得更多
A lot more blood and a lot more sweat.
希望不是我们的人 老伙计
Hopefully not any of ours, old boy.
我想没有你 我们是做不到的 比利
I don't think we can do this without you, Billy.
好吧 如果你愿意 我也愿意
Well, I'm up for it if you are.
我们需要你的拖船
I think we're gonna need your tug.
海西和我将沿着海港散步
Haysey and I will take a stroll along the harbor
并消灭所有在巡逻的士兵
and take out any soldiers still patrolling.
弗雷迪会把他的小艇开过来
Freddy will bring his dinghy around
并照顾好S艇
and take care of the S-boats.
我们在拖船旁等你
We'll meet you by the tug boats.
公爵夫人呢
And the Duchessa?
这就是苹果和我
That's Apple and me.
我们会照顾好所有船员并抛锚
We'll take care of any crew and blow the anchor.
摧毁他们的通讯设备
And destroy their comms.
不知道你会在船上遇到什么
Not sure what you'll meet on board.
带上我的上司和另外两个手下
Take my top boy and two more of my men.
先生们 开始准备吧
Gentlemen, let's prepare.
哦 鲨鱼 宝贝
Oh, the shark, babe
凌厉的牙齿 亲爱的
Has such teeth, dear
向他们展示了洁白的珍珠
And he shows them pearly white
就像一把小刀
Just a jack-knife
亲爱的老麦克希斯
Has old MacHeath, dear
把它藏在看不见的地方
And he keeps it out of sight
你知道鲨鱼什么时候咬人吗
You know when that shark bites
用他的锋利牙齿 亲爱的
With his teeth, dear
猩红色的波浪开始蔓延
Scarlet billows starts to spread
漂亮的服饰 穿着老麦克希斯的服饰 亲爱的
Fancy gloves, oh, wears old MacHeath, dear
所以从来没有一丝红色
So there's never, never a trace of red
在人行道上
On the sidewalk
星期天早上 你还不知
On Sunday morning, don't you know
好似说谎
Lies a body
渗出的生命
Oozing life
有人在拐角处鬼鬼祟祟地走来走去
And someone sneakin' around the corner
那会是老麦克刀吗
Could that be old Mack the Knife?
有一艘拖船
There's a tug boat
在河边 你不知吗
Down by the river, don't cha know
就好似在那一刻一泻千里
Where a cement bag's just a-drooping on down...
还没有
Not yet.
我的先生
Mein Herr.
海斯
Haysey...
在左边 长官
Up there on the left, sir.
是的
Yes.
他发出了撞击声
He made a crash!
我们可以开那辆车 长官 给我们省点鞋皮
We could take that car, sir. Save us some shoe leather.
小心 老麦回来了
Look out, old Macky is back
来了
Incoming.
请出示证件
Papers please.
指挥官 没事吧 弗雷迪
- Commander. - All good, Freddy?
准备就绪
Charges are set to go
一旦我们离开港口 长官
once we're out of the harbor, sir.
那我们继续吧
Let's carry on then.
喜欢你的礼物吗
Did you enjoy your gift?
嗯
Mmm.
我想现在是时候了
I think now it's time
狐狸向狐狸精展示自己的巢穴
that the fox shows his den to the vixen.
苍鹭 为什么灯还亮着
Heron, why are the lights still on?
我用油灯点亮了房间
I lit the room with oil lamps,
这样他们就不会注意到停电
so they wouldn't notice when the power went out.
小心
Look out!
弗莱迪 操纵这辆88
Freddy, rig this 88,
然后和海斯一起拉第一下
then take the first tug with Haysey.
晚上好 晚上好
- Gute nacht. - Guten abend.
晚上好
Guten abend.
非常抱歉 老伙计
Terribly sorry, old boy.
你介意吗 我好像
Do you mind? I seem to...
我的刀插错地方了
...have misplaced my knife.
讨厌
Bugger!
谢谢你 比利
Thank you, Billy.
哦
Oh!
我希望那不是你的血 拉森
I hope that's not your blood, Lassen.
我也希望如此
I hope so too.
好了 伙计们 出发吧
Okay, boys, cast off.
把船开走吧
Let's get this ship out of here.
走吧 走吧
Go on. Go on...
走
Go on!
像这样的房间还有三个
There's three more rooms just like this one.
应该能在接下来的六个月里阻止U型潜艇
That should stop the U-boats for the next six months.
把这东西拖走吧
Let's get this thing towed out of here.
我们在这里 伙计们
We are here, boys.
别出声设个警告
Quietly. Let's set a warning.
我需要你到船头去
I need you to go to the front of the boat
并将火神号连接到公爵夫人号上
and attach the Vulcan to the Duchessa,
拉森和我去桥上
Lassen and I will head to the bridge.
好的
Okay.
走右边
Take the right side.
而你 上台 开始吧
And you, get up there and get this thing started.
是格斯
It's Gus.
每个人都已就位
Everyone's in place.
什么
What,
你不会真以为这样能行吧
you didn't actually think it would work, did you?
这是你的计划
It was your plan.
那么 让我们确保
Well, let's make sure
遵守的约定
we keep our end of the bargain.
发信号回来 我就离开
Signal back and I'll heave off.
那么 现在该怎么办
So, what happens now?
我们等着锚链爆炸
We wait for the anchor chain to blow.
预计什么时候呢
When do we expect that to happen?
我希望很快
Shortly, I hope.
然后我们就可以击沉她
And then we're free to take her.
然而 一旦燃料库消失 比赛就开始了
However, the real race begins once the fuel depot goes.
到时候岛上所有的士兵都会出现
Then we'll have every soldier on the island turning up.
我们可不想亲眼目睹这一切
We don't wanna be around to witness that.
保险丝有多长
How long was that fuse
你的锚链是什么
you attached to the anchor chain?
我们很快就会知道
We'll find out soon enough.
等着吧 你会抓住绳子的
Wait for it, you're gonna catch the rope.
来吧
Come on.
第一张多米诺骨牌倒下
First domino falls.
接另一条线 是 老板
- Hitch up the other line. - Yes, boss.
挑起重担
Pick up the slack.
他们必须在燃料库爆炸前转移
They need to move her before the fuel dump blows.
赫伦 我们需要马乔
Heron, we need Marjorie.
交给我吧
Leave Marjorie to me.
我们会赶上你的
We'll catch you up.
非常好
Very good.
我们走吧
Let's go!
我不得不说 小姐
I have to say, Fraulein,
你很正点
you were good.
你很狡猾
And you were sly.
只有两种人
There are only two types of people
像狐狸一样狡猾
that are as sly as the fox.
德国人
The German
犹太人
and the Jew.
你也不是德国人
And you are not German.
我想现在是时候
I think now it's time...
开始真正的派对
...for a real party.
这本不该发生
That wasn't supposed to happen yet.
把她铐起来
Shackle her!
跟我来
And follow me.
港口受到攻击
The harbor is under attack!
他们来了
They're coming.
我们需要引擎的动力
We need power on the engine.
太重了 把她扶起来
- She's too heavy! - Pick up the slack!
等等
Wait...
她不动了
She's not moving!
开火 开火 开火
Fire! Fire! Fire!
等着瞧吧
Wait for it.
我们需要更强的引擎动力
We need more power on the engine.
给我更多的动力 更多的动力
Give me more power! More power!
这就对了 它开始动了
That's it, it's working!
就是这样
That's it!
准备就绪
Ready!
海斯
Haysey!
我们现在离开射程了
We're out of range now.
我不是专家
I'm no expert.
但你肩膀上有个伤口 海斯
But you've got a big old hole in your shoulder, Haysey.
队长
Captain,
你能给我解释一下 怎么回事吗
would you explain to me what's going on here?
动力消失了
The power is gone.
燃料库遭到破坏
The fuel depot has been sabotaged.
没有人知道发生了什么
And no one knows what's happening.
但这是你的错
But this is your fault.
我的船在哪里
Where is my ship?
公爵夫人号 她去哪儿了
The Duchessa, where did it go?
有人趁你不注意 开走了
Someone's taken him while you weren't looking.
你个白痴
You idiot!
你总得解释一下
You always have to say something
在非常错误的时间
at the very wrong time.
和你一起永远都是错的
There is never a right time with you!
你的贪婪和变态
Your greed and perversion
让你分心了
has distracted you from your duties.
现在 我的海港被毁了
Now my harbor is destroyed.
船也不见了
And my ship is gone!
现在你也走吧 谢谢了
And now you're gone too. Thank you.
令人印象深刻
Impressive.
听起来你的雷管起作用了
Sounds like your detonators worked.
干杯 小姐
Chapeau, mademoiselle.
你弹得很好 真是个狐狸精
You play well. You really are the vixen.
是吗
Am I?
我都已经坦诚相待了
Well, my hand's been revealed.
现在怎么办
So, what now?
现在 我拥有了你
Now, I possess your hand
以及你对我所做的一切
and for everything you have done to me,
我将千倍奉还
I will visit a thousand fold upon you.
是啊
Yeah.
但是没用
But no.
躺下
Lie down.
格斯 我们不能再等了
Gus, we can't wait much longer.
他们来了
They're coming.
如果我们留在这里
If we stay here,
会与其他人失去联系
we'll lose contact with the others.
坚持住 比利
Hold fast, Billy.
苍鹭和玛乔丽都有自己的生存之道
Heron has a way of surviving and Marjorie,
好吧 祝你好运
well... good luck with that.
有一艘巡逻艇向我们驶来
That's a patrol boat coming towards us.
格斯 我们必须离开 现在就走
Gus, we need to leave. Now.
等等
Hold on...
是他们
It's them.
RH.
KB.马乔里
- KB. - Marjorie.
真是穿得又多又少
Overdressed and underdressed at the same time.
来吧 让我们把你解救出来
Come on, let's get you out of those shackles.
进来 维奥莱特
Come in, Violet.
呼叫 "紫罗兰号"
Calling H.M.S. Violet.
收到 维奥莱特
Come in, Violet.
这是伴娘
This is Maid Honor.
说吧 伴娘
Go ahead, Maid Honor.
开免提
Loudspeaker.
对不起 这么晚了还打扰您
Sorry to bother you at this time of the night,
但我们发现有一两个项目
but we've found ourselves with one or two items
您可能会感兴趣
that might be of interest to you.
我们可以会合交接吗
Shall we rendezvous for a handover?
给我接庞德上将
Get me Admiral Pound.
什么事 长官
- Yes? - Sir,
好消息和坏消息 是的 说吧
- good news and bad news. - Yes, yes. Get to it.
坏消息是 他们没有击沉她
Bad news, they didn't sink her.
好消息
Good news,
他们偷走了她
they stole her.
祝贺你 首相
Congratulations, Prime Minister.
别动
Hold it there!
指挥官
Commander.
庞德上将命令你
You were ordered by Admiral Pound
停止活动
to cease activities.
你却没有
You did not.
因此 你们将被送回英国
Therefore, you are to be returned to England
面对法庭
to face a tribunal. You.
你与其他民兵一起返回拖船
Return to your tug with the rest of your militia.
把他们带到船上去 长官
- Take them to the brig. - Sir!
我也很高兴见到你 指挥官
Good to see you too, Commander.
真有个性
Separate cells.
跟我来
Follow me!
出发吧 我们走
Let's go! Let's get moving!
RH. KB.
- RH. - KB.
来吧
Come on.
快走
Go on, move.
请稍等 水手
One moment, seaman.
比利
Billy.
一只眼睛盯着边界
One eye on the boundary...
一只眼睛盯着酒馆
One eye on the pub.
总有一天 他们会为此感谢你的
They'll thank you for this one day.
我不确定
I'm not sure
这才是我们真正要找的 不是吗
that's what we were really looking for, was it,
殿下
Your Highness?
少校 商店随时为您开放
Shop's open for you anytime, Major.
抱歉 打扰了 首相
Sorry to intrude, Prime Minister,
但M认为你应该看看这个
but M thought you should see this.
谢谢你 格洛丽亚
Thank you, Gloria.
列队面向前方
Line up. Face front!
没必要大喊大叫
No need to shout.
站着别动
Stand still!
能喝杯茶吗
Any chance of a cup of tea?
你 退到墙边
You, back up to the wall.
把手拿开 小菜鸟
Off the cloth, moth.
站直
Stand straight!
高级军事人员
Never before have the senior Military
从未和海军指挥官一起
and Navy Commanders of this country
他们的谴责如此一致
been so united in their condemnation.
他们认为
It is their view
认为该纪律
that the discipline
我们的武装部队赖以生存
on which our armed forces depends
被不为服从之人所破坏
has been undermined by men serving no master
而是他们对鲜血 谋杀和混乱的渴求
but their own thirst for blood, murder and mayhem.
不服从命令之人
Men who disobeyed a direct order
来自舰队司令本人
from the Admiral of the fleet himself,
而选择了
and chose instead
相信心血来潮的直觉
to trust the whim and intuition
还有站在他身边的人
of the man standing beside him.
他们怎么敢
How dare they.
今天上午
When only this morning,
第一批美国士兵抵达英国领土
the first American soldiers arrived on British soil,
和我们并肩作战
ready to stand shoulder to shoulder
和我们一起在欧洲
with us in Europe.
冒死横渡北大西洋的盟军
Allies who risked death crossing the North Atlantic,
只有奇迹出现
and only by some miracle
发现纳粹U型潜艇并没有给他们带来麻烦
found their crossing untroubled by Nazi U-boats.
我可以补充 这是一个令人高兴的情况
A happy circumstance, I might add,
无法解释
which cannot be accounted for,
但却为美国扫清了道路
but which has cleared the way for the United States
参加欧洲战争
to enter the European war.
我知道
And for which I know
罗斯福总统将不胜感激
President Roosevelt to be immeasurably grateful.
但是
But setting aside
撇开这一笔无法解释的财富
this stroke of unexplained fortune,
如何处置这支桀骜不驯的队伍
what is to be done with this unruly company
谁不服从命令
who do not obey orders?
似乎已经无关紧要
Who seem to have formed
属于他们的战争之师
their own ministry of ungentlemanly warfare.
现在开始 将被纳入麾下
From now on, they work for me.